junglejar.com 2005-02-07

# JungleJar.com :. Independent Electronic Music

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Thank you for visiting the JungleJar.com website. Protecting consumer privacy is very important to us. Our Online Privacy Statement is available to inform you about our collection and use of personal information so that you can make informed choices about how your own information is collected and used. This Online Privacy Statement reflects the JungleJar.com policies covering personal information collected at this website. We collect information on behalf of our business clients. For example, we use consumer information every day to ensure fast and accurate processing money transfers. In addition, JungleJar.com strives to better serve our customers by offering goods and services that we believe fit their needs and interests. When identifying an opportunity, JungleJar.com may use consumer information it has collected in an effort to identify consumers who may be interested in that opportunity. Central to that is ensuring that we abide by a set of privacy policies, which are outlined below. These policies guide us in the collection and use of information as well as employee responsibilities in protecting your privacy. We use personal information about consumers only in a manner consistent with these policies.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

JungleJar.com collects personal information in order to offer or provide goods and services to consumers and our customers. We may obtain this information from a variety of sources: · Directly from customer applications, questionnaires and other materials submitted to us by customers; · From transactions in which JungleJar.com and consumers are involved; · From clickthru activity on our web sites; and · From a variety of third-party sources, such as our business customers, government repositories, consumer reporting agencies and other financial institutions.

**

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

**

JungleJar.com does not disclose customer information to third parties without first giving customers an opportunity to opt-out of certain kinds of disclosures. There are some disclosures to third parties that are not subject to the opt-out, such as disclosures necessary to effect, administer or enforce a transaction requested by you, to companies that perform services for us or to prevent fraud. Finally, JungleJar.com may disclose information about former customers to third parties and companies with which JungleJar.com is affiliated. Those disclosures may consist of the following: · Financial background information describing a customer's financial status; · Identification information, such as name and address data; · Transaction information, such as account activity, debit activity or credit activity; and · Other information relating to financial matters.

**

WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF PERSONAL CONSUMER INFORMATION.

**

JungleJar.com limits access to personal information to those employees of JungleJar.com and its affiliates who need it to fulfill their business responsibilities. Employees must adhere to JungleJar.com privacy policies. Employees violating these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that sensitive personal information is safeguarded.

**

WE USE APPROPRIATE SECURITY SAFEGUARDS.

**

At JungleJar.com, security is a priority. We employ appropriate measures to protect consumer information against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include, among others, encryption, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. JungleJar.com continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.   

**  
THE JungleJar.com WEBSITE IS NOT DIRECTED AT CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.**

Our website is not directed at children under the age of 13 and JungleJar.com does not collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13.

**

WEBSITE MAY BE LINKED TO OTHER WEBSITES

**

JungleJar.com may create links to third party websites. JungleJar.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by websites that are linked from our website.

**

OPT OUT RIGHT

**

JungleJar.com may disclose consumer information to third parties as described earlier in this notice. We strive to give consumers choices about how their data will be used. You have the right to opt-out of (direct us not to make) these disclosures when the consumer information is about you. Of course, there are some disclosures to third parties that are not subject to the opt-out, such as disclosures necessary to effect, administer or enforce a transaction requested by you, to companies that perform services for us or to prevent fraud. When you use this service, you will be asked whether you wish to opt out. We may alter this statement as needed for certain products and services and to abide by local laws or regulations. JungleJar.com reserves the right to amend or modify this statement from time to time. We urge you to review this statement whenever you visit in order to obtain the most current statement.
